Martin Sekeres

Dewar Grove Rugby, CV21

Phone: 07740334976

Email: mar.sekeres@gmail.com
GitHub: github.com/martinsekeras
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/martinsekeres
Portfolio: martinsekeras.github.io

PERSONAL PROFILE

A 3rd year computer games programming student seeking a 12 month placement in Games or software development. I have been tinkering with games since I was 12 years old. Started with Java, Modding Minecraft then moved to HTML and CSS and finally landed at computer games programming using mainly C++, C# using Unity and Visual Studio 2017 / 2019.

ACADEMIC SKILLS

- Programming Skills in C++, C#, Visual Basic gained from my University Degree.
- Database building using Microsoft Access which I used in college doing my HNC in Computer Systems Development.
- Video Editing using After Effects & Adobe Flash Animator which i gained from personal projects.
- Technical writing skills from having to write troubleshooting guides, and user manuals.
- Knowledge of MS Office, MS Visio, Adobe CC, GIMP, VMware also mostly gained from personal use.

EDUCATION

De Montfort University, Leicester - *1st Class Hons BSc* in Computer Games Programming (*Predicted*), *2:1 Worst Case Scenario*

2018 - Current

Year 1 Modules

Intro to C++ Programming (94%)

Intro to OOP in C++ (86%)

Computer Ethics (74%)

Computer Law and Cyber Security (56%)

Computer Systems (60%)

Computer Networks (48%)

Game Architectures and Design (76%)

Game Prototype Design (73%)

Year 2 Modules

Applied Mechanics (59%)

OOP in C++ (78%)

Advanced OOP in C++ (68)

3D Modeling (66%)

Intro to Shaders (69%)

Dev Strategies for Mobile Games (65%)

Mobile Games Development (71%)

Al for Simulation (73%)

Year 3 Modules (Current Year)

Game Engine Architecture (63%)

Fuzzy Logic & KBS (62%)

Multi-Service Networks 1 (72%)

Mobile Robotics (64%)

Multi-Service Networks 2 (60%)

Game Engine Development (52%)

Development Project (70% Predicted)

North Warwickshire & Hinckley College, Nuneaton - HNC in Computer Systems

Development

09 2016 - 06 2018

William Bradford Academy, Earl Shilton - 2 GCSEs graded C in Maths and English, 2

Level 2 BTECs, 2 Level 3 BTECs (P) & 1 RSA in Science (P)

09 2011 - 07 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cleaner

SolviT Recruitment, Rugby

02 2021 - Current

Performing various jobs for SolviT Recruitment as cleaner.

1. EV Cargo through PFM

- a. Cleaning Toilets
- b. Hoovering
- c. Moping
- d. Wiping surfaces and touch points.
- e. Emptying bins
- f. Refilling toilet paper & hand paper

2. Eddie Stobart Truck Stop

- a. Moping
- b. Hoovering
- c. Cleaning showers and bathrooms
- d. Emptying bins
- e. Refilling toilet paper & hand paper
- f. Cleaning of surfaces

Cleaner

Servest, Earl Shilton

May 2014 - Sept 2016

- Responsible for cleaning part of primary school;
 - o sweeping,
 - o mopping,
 - o dusting,
 - wiping of surfaces,
 - o emptying bins,
 - o hoovering,
- Using machines such as floor buffers to polish the floors.
- Sticking to tight deadlines every evening in a very busy environment.

REFERENCES

Available on request.